all right yeah let me uh take my
controllers in yeah I'm just hoping the
controllers is just like straight up
work that's that's something I always
like find like you know this this will
work okay but before we get
started I think we need to lay down a
few ground rules at least for this
session competitive gameplay was a
mistake yeah it really was let's try to
not be toxic so like if you get hit or
if you die uh don't try to actually take
anyone's things if it happens it happens
but like don't go for it uh don't blow
up anyone's bombs or bomb another player
if you can help
it don't uh don't Boomerang them a
million times because I know you love to
do that last
time here we are on level three now
finally laying out the ground rules for
this competitive gameplay well this you
know these may not track into the future
sessions but at least for this one we'll
see how it goes if we need more toxicity
in our life you know we can we can
always amp it up there's unlimited
toxicity out
there yeah let's see if we can at least
try to do that keep things a little
uh oh dingle's here
again did we do that last time I don't
think we did yes that was the
um um oh that's right the around Dark
World a million times to avoid you
basically oh it make a whole lot more
sense if you had four players because
like with just two players it's pretty
rough I gotta remember how that
didn't
y I've kidnapped myself blue is a
traitor got got to try to grab one of
them this looks like the last
Temple like in
uh what is
it Link to the Past isn't this like the
look at the the temple the top of the
world
something
or
oh finding all these
secrets yeah a look at that I'm rich
wow already
toxic although I didn't say anything
about grabbing other people so guess
that's
fair like oh shoot I missed the the
window of putting down the ground
rules oh no I've
expired a you're about to
expire D I miss my red
oh
NOP is purple having purple's having
some issues there yeah he's uh a little
worse for we oh God D oh wow that I
don't think you get any ey frames you
get hit by not me I'm rich you're like
instant no you don't you have no ey
frames on these
my
Diner no come back money I need you oh
is it it's based on where you're walking
okay so it's a it's a m got it I thought
it was a
tiny money Chuck Ching here we go a he's
Rich oh it's Boomerang you got to pick
that
up
see I'm just still wondering what the
heck is up with purple
he's uh he's feeling a little off today
you
know purple do you need help just blink
twice blink twice if
you oh okay that's what we're
doing watch out Agony mama is behind
you I those guys aren't even guys
anymore don't we have to like Boomerang
them to
kill no these guys are just bumpers
yes they don't even hurt
you I guess we can probably push them in
the
hole if you don't get pushed in first of
course try
to why am I shooting One Direction I
think
it's do we use them as like Shield or
something ohill one how you do that oh
you just uh you just give them is given
what's
for we need them to get through this
though uh looks like
it yeah but like I'm
rich I'm not
here I'm not here doing all the the
heavy lifting the group project is all
me heavy lifting with the big
gems that's about it a it's teasing us
in that direction you see that what is
this they're not supposed to
all the way back wow that's
brutal gave us like kind of zoom out
look at that look at
that fancy effect come
on you got to you got to sometimes take
in the
air how do we get over
there we I kill the guy
what here let me throw
you go get him boy go really I was like
there's no way that'll Miss get there's
a dude over
here is this this this to do from the
other
room I see they do fall
[Music]
off just stand on
this oh is this I guess we could try to
push
him something tells we were supposed to
him but why put four of them
I like six of
them see the trick is he still get
hitting oh fairy please come I know I
think I can Boomerang it I just suppose
a I think that's it I think I die from
that no oh I
didn't dang it knocked my clock
off they're like the gimmick isn't over
there's more gimmick just keep yeah
that's our floor for getting
back it's fine
we oh no problem I'll take that
I can't believe I actually jump that's
the
question
God oh you
can I'm
rich I found out where we're supposed to
go yeah
look hitting hitting purple is not going
to fix him I think he's been hit a
little too much
already oh nice hit you got both of them
and I got both of these and he pushed
down can't believe the toxicity the
unintentional
toxicity oh found a hole so oh wait
where am I going just keep going
Z can't jump
over hey how you
doing I think we go
down I'm really surprised we don't uh I
found a
key and I found some
money oh I
see is there more over
here oh I found a heart yeah I kind of
guess you're the one needs it this
time
um I don't know if I can jump that
do we even know where we need to BL
key yes there's a key door up the
top don't know how to do that I really
can't jump
that a man I'm going to have blue Dy
just for or [ __ ] some Google I
guess how the heck do I get out of this
place oh there's a there's a thing up
here there's buttons on the on the top
level that's all fun Andy but I'm still
stuck down how'd you get out of here I
just found a way out I got
good you say you got good and you didn't
get the AR okay I mean I got the key the
key is more
important key is temporary hard is
forever I man that's that's some real
poetry right
there can I just push this guy can I
push you do he does he get hurt no ah he
does wow push I don't think you're
supposed to do that but
sure look at that on just there you
goink that may not be the best place to
can all right now how do we get over
there oh I found out how we got over
there hey I'm
rich be kind of annoying time
that oh we got a boss oh we got a real
boss all I have is a jump which I guess
we can jump in O okay but like slap you
oh yeah that's right we can do the
ground I'm
rich uh congrats on your fake curreny
it's only Fiat you don't want to worry
about it
here's the oh that switches
direction is that this little eye thing
you wanted that is that what you want
you're responsible for hitting the ey
thing now wow you just blocked me nope
wasn't me yeah how do you get back do
you uh is it in the chest maybe I can
throw and then uh you got to swep to
that guy there you go like
technically what the eye thing the IE
thing
wow oh it just drops J it's worthless oh
don't want to do that that
actually that what' you pick
up hey want some
cool say anything about 30 dials I got
how did I fall down did you see that
like hit the pot and I just slipped
down oh that's a long one guess it's
karma you know what it's definitely the
play to do the uh the jumping there
because this is kind of
ridiculous you know what you can have
this I don't think I can even if I want
it I do want I do want my fake currency
it can't be helped a monkey brain needs
it lizard brain says number go up monkey
brain says this is how we get big
number oh what was that you only you can
get that anyways do you
mind like fight me over something you've
already I thought I had a slash it to
get
it oh what down a hole oh they found
some stuff this
what you got down there Jam right here
oh we need
bombs do we I make you say that there's
a bombable wall next to
me probably just a secret it's like
maybe the power bracelet or
something yeah you need the power
bracelet wristband or whatever it's
called what's in there anything good
oh what'd you get hey actually you were
on top did you you play this game before
haven't you yeah that's little you know
I played the whole game in between
stream actually a 30 hour game all ah
you pick
right yeah think I know what happen I
think I did the jump forward earlier
when I thought I slipped wow my K
believe that hit
me
um that was the worst outcome I don't
think I actually want bombs for this I
think the bow go
back I'm keeping the jump I'm sure there
might be other like Secrets if we have
the
bomb but then
like why do I need
them the bow has combat
wow these uh these things are like off
cycle that's kind of
annoying I'll uh I'll be over there one
[Music]
day that was
no s me back in that
fire I knew it
you're
right defeat
schmuck guy over here oh okay it only
stuns him that's
right oh he's actually attacking back
this
time hey money that's not too bad
[Music]
wow almost fell off oh K
him I pick him
up St is the reason if I can pick up
other who can pick up dark right no he's
special he has AI
Powers H
cycle wait where
wait what you I
kill no there was still another one left
well yeah it was he was blue and I was
uh I was blue I had a Blue on
Blue that doesn't make sense how can you
how can you be
blue aren't you already Blue
Link you can get
that oh there's a dude here
yeah oh this isn't good I brought my
Bombs all this way and then I drop them
I went right through the lava too and I
thought I had a good plan I was going to
use them on the monster around here you
should watch out for them I mean if they
uh they can toast me they're sure to
burn you to crisp oh hey I can teach you
an incredible way of dealing with those
pesky things what do you say would you
like to hear it
I need a yes
no you bet great I'll show you the
problem is that these things have skin
as hard as a rock even with my strength
it's a waste of time to hit them I can't
even make a dent but then it came to me
they may be tough on the outside but
weak on the inside so right then I open
their mouths and breathe and to breathe
fire Gulp and then blam what a great
idea but then I dropped my bombs in the
lava uh I can't believe
it okay so then the question is think
have to go back
for
no yeah this is kind of like all your
second
unless there's like a hole we can jump
down maybe the bomb in a
hole I'm guessing that is what we
need this
S I feel like there's I think we just
jumped in there right uh before it
happens do it all like that ah there's
the bombs you're you're on bomb
Duty now you know what happened last
time you chose to forgo The crucial boss
fighting weapon
oh I fell down you might very well need
it I mean you already know that they're
not going to be able to be damaged with
your weapons he might to go grab
bombs watch it I'm going to need the the
feather here in the next uh next level
that wow look at me getting rid of all
my health before the boss is that like
what Dark Souls people do make sure
you're minimum help just playing Dark
Souls that's
all so they just need to walk into the
oh never mind they literally open their
MTH ah you
missed oh got one
they seem to be time so I think they
doing the same
work oh no little crusty on no no no
it's um just how it's supposed to
be
got I guess you can like put down a bomb
I guess they only open up your mouth I
guess if within range cuz that one dude
on the far left just not open
m there's like just barely enough time
for the bomb down go the M if you're in
like a really good
spot pretty much better off just
constantly refreshing
no I accidentally did the Dr
Button yeah the controls are like easy
to
forget it's also really
easy NOP oh okay H this one at
all nice
I did the final blow in all of
them I'm two pe's in a pod two bullets
in a MAG two cannibal
midgets oh I guess if you had
uh what up with my sword did you see
that no that wasn't a sword oh here we
go the story time I'll let you get I'll
let you have that this one
[Music]
who ho link danger has struck Hyrule
Castle once again oh it's player two why
don't you do this oh all right why did I
give it to you that's quite a good
question the darkness we thought
vanquished has returned perhaps some
dark agent REM remained hidden waiting
for the right moment to strike what a
convenient plot
point where there is great evil through
there may also be an imprisoned Shrine
Maiden you must tell the maiden of this
Tower we cannot abandon Hyrule
Castle all right that's crazy how like
all the evil is just concentrated right
here where the shrine maidens are in
prison there's no evil anywhere else in
the world no no no like like no one's
robbing no one's burglarizing no one's
doing anything think of that nope here's
here's a story
drop that was much of a boss
no not
really I mean it was unique I appreciate
their attempt at like giving you a new
unique mechanic for each boss or
fight you pass through the Flames to
rescue
me such bravery you're just like the
Knights of high rule got like you know
super slow it's it's awful
you've heard of the Knights of Hyrule of
course they're the pride of the Kingdom
they would lay down their lives for
Honor so how's your
day and Hyrule four sacred Jewels can
open the path to the realm of the
heavens it's just like super jarring how
how much time is given for this this is
made for fouryear old old who never
played a Zelda game before and it's like
like the owl was speaking just fine the
Goron spoke fine but not this person
this is critical important story bits
those
weren't the safety of these Jewels has
for ages been entrusted to the Knights
of
Hyrule and yet in these dark
times the knights are nowhere to be
seen I cannot hide by
fears pardon Master Kora Gora you
say is that so well then we must go to
Hyrule
Castle we must Liberate the
castle oh it's it's a little redone but
yeah who was Kora Gora again I know he
was in Ocarina of Time I think
yeah yeah I have no clue I have no clue
[Music]
[Applause]
great
one oh it's like you're just forced
right into your assign spot oh really I
was in the bottom left and I was looking
at it and it's all purple there I'm like
huh yeah what's up with this something's
wrong
here remember we play by golf rules in
this one
so yeah but the game does it
lives
lost I died like a bunch of times I
wasn't really careful I died
once for it's such like like everything
just relies on this and like there's no
other metrics or
bonuses yeah if they really wanted to
make it brutal well I guess the idea is
that this would be split between four
people and not just two yeah it's like
you would technically have half of what
you got know how
to I I didn't steal anything from you
you
[Music]
know I got to this is the the only thing
I that's going going my way in life
right now so I I need this I need this
little rise go back to playing some Mar
[Music]
party let's do some uh King Buu
sabotaging again
you know because if hyro Castle couldn't
have been used once but what do we used
it
twice well when you're like cartridge is
32 kilobytes like 2 megabytes you kind
of have to squeeze it all in you know or
this would have been on a
disc the game did Disc so they had like
a gig in size available to them that's
like you know 10 Hole uh in 64 games or
something like that I don't know you're
right yeah no I mean you can get like
up to was it up to
10 it was it was I think it's like 1
like two one and 1.2 gigs or something
like that for the uh the GameCube disc
oh okay cuz they were like the mini disc
for whatever
reason what's that girl doing out there
all by herself link please you must
something with her if she stays out
there alone she's bound to be ATT tack
you must something with her
link I
didn't that's a naughty void link
spamming you know uh excuse me were you
just talking to a green fairy that's
kind of cringe bro like that's a little
unnecessary do you really need to do
that in the middle of the open I saw it
there was a beautiful fairy fluttering
around you but I mean it was still kind
of cringe to talk to it amazing what a
papa told me really is true but it's
still kind of cringe what is that that's
not how you spell
papaa like Po no I mean I think it was
supposed to be Papa but like what the
never seen it like that he said good
boys and girls get to meet fairies I
mean sometimes so but when you get kind
of old though it's little gets uh look
gets dated like today I like the like
Zelda lore is that you never get to see
fairies unless you have to be like the
hen or whatever you call them so yeah
there's some spitting facts out there
like today I was coming home after
running errands and then I tripped on
some cringe but I couldn't get back
because I tripped on the cringe I mean
it's started raining and the castle
guards were moving all the Cannons I
mean it was kind of cool and everything
uh the Cannons are really old but
they're not meant to be used they're all
decorative in the ceremonial it was
really weird uh for the ceremony start
say if you're all going on ahe uh take
me with you please that's your bag not
M your friends with the green fairies so
of course it's okay right I mean czy
logic I'm just like tol in my hair over
here thinking about
it I can actually say no don't say
no the good ending is always when you
say
yes all right great but don't talk about
some cringe skibby crap over here I'll
die my name is
meon I'm from one of the other games but
you didn't worry about me and this is
the prequel to those other games but
we're not going to talk about
thatmore well they they've had that in
multiple other games
I'm from lawn La ranch right up the
road why did the voice suddenly change
Malon was in the I mean I know she was
in no it's not that's not in Major's
mask it's
um um the it's another name more GE Mas
I least know she's in Ocarina time she
say she's in other games yeah was she
like the model is in in Jor mask but
she's called something different she's
also in um Link's Awakening as well
gets uh she gets around if you if you
know what I
mean no
don't wait does she survive the fire
no look at you
dude you're an awful
Guardian go
girl pick her up slow wait
okay I can pick I can pick up a darn
fish lady I why oh oh oh bro you just
like going to kill
her just stay in
there can you pick up the you have to do
all the heavy
lifting wait a minute this guy actually
kind of kill me well I got I got this
girl over here and she's um she's mad
out of like fine glass or something like
that I don't know wait I can I got her
stuck she's stuck she's safe she's safe
cuz she's stuck
oh yeah you really can't pick I
know these guys are like kind of tough
got to get them at they are trained
Warriors I'm going to be doing the darn
group project over here while you're
making
money what do you mean I am doing the
group what do you think that was killing
those guys was the group project all
you're doing is coasting along with the
your follower which you got to bring
over
here girl you been doing the one job
come on girl is kind of
cringe oh okay that wasn't
earing Popa he's the pope of this
world that's what they say in Italy they
go po po po when the pop comes
around okay oh M you're late the rain's
coming down so hard I was beginning to
worry in fact I'd gotten so worried that
I was about to go looking for you that's
crazy that it's like
you know there's a threshold there and
he was like yeah it's fine raining
stormy thundering outside ah she was
just playing the mud like demons taking
over the castle you know no big deal to
tell the truth Popa these young boys
rescued
me okay well hang on a second I thought
she was the little
girl yeah you to see where the um see
where the little um uh whisker the
little like bubble the th bubble the the
speak Buckle That's So
speaking like soldiers in the castle
were behaving so oddly and I couldn't
get past
them they were moving the old canons
around and they even aimed their bows at
me the like speech bubble is really
weird you can kind of see how they did
it though it's like the two Sprites I
mean let's be real here like this this
this game this product is weird like
it's using like effects from like Wind
Waker like all the fancy effects that
they made and then they're like shoving
it on top of like Sprites from cobbled
together from other games essentially
and then like updated Sprites like Goron
Sprites didn't exist and the darn links
Awakening or links to the pass so I mean
when you put it that way it almost feels
like a fan-made game it really does like
when you like think about this game like
this thing like how does this exist is
it's it's like a tech demo that got like
good polish oh we're getting a horse oh
cast guards are sure to be headed this
way and
there are more ahead too we'll be much
safer riding my Swift horses I'm sure
our farm is right next door we have lots
of carrots around so take some with you
those horses love carrots they come
running if you got some handy think you
once again I'll never forget what You'
done his eyes are like looking in
different directions it's a little
concerning he's an
idiot is that we Vigilant very he's very
vigilant
I didn't think about it like that oh
what you got there that's cool I'm going
to come down there no you don't you
don't you
don't you don't it's Mario Luigi that's
that's really saying like that huh
[Music]
I guess I'm a
boomerang I'm a I'm a boomerang I'm a
boomer I'm an elevated level
Boomer well I don't know what we can do
down there
but I know what we can do down I mean
did you notice that they also stayed
outside oh there's a
thing a [ __ ] there's things in here oh
there's money in here I'm this is their
money I'm taking their life
[Music]
savings their life savings contain the
heart of a of their dead mother
apparently a little morbid but you know
are you supposed to hammer these things
does that work
NOP wow when you're like out of the GBA
version you get like super
huh that's suspicious though right this
isn't the case of like we got to move
our house oh look there's a
thing yeah I mean that's how we get the
chest well I hope that sign didn't have
anything important on
it oh can we do the house you want to
try
it oh oh you
can
s garbage
dang I swear to God get out get out of
here what are you
doing oh my God I did the whole group
you almost stole from me I got one
Hearts I almost had the other
Heart come over here you got to flatten
you and then it's Mario Luigi stuff over
here I can't roll when do that for so
long i' expect it to be for like two
seconds but that's like ages carrots for
your horses help yourself take a carrot
y wow that is a
gigantic how did you get that
toxicity where' you get those carrots
from from the holy
[ __ ] where'd you get that at that's the
real
question why are you holding
it how the heck did you get a oh I see
you hit to throw
oh let's
go actually I bet there's like a
secret oh it's timed that's pretty lame
should really just let you have for the
rest of the game no no I'm kind of
curious how like isn't visible or
Invincible oh this is the same as the
cor thing what a
way when we like change location
maybe Little M
yeah okay I fig it was probably
something it does look like so long as
we don't stop nope
that wait there's something back there
though oh there's carrots up here okay
there's probably just a
[Music]
one this is
awkward yeah a little unfair if you ask
me I like snap back you see
D I'm digging
it wow they really uh oh can't can't let
that one
go you stole from me stole from you I
was the only one down
there my eyes lead clean to it why my
eyes saw it but even before you mentally
knew it that it was supposed to be yours
I I acquired It
Anyways ah ah he's a he's acing
me it's like every two has
one I don't know he's learning from his
mistakes
um
that's dang you stole my first place
with that yeah somehow I came out on
top tingle times volume
[Music]
three I'm
yeah getting some dialog
there there a
button you going to read that out
loud yeah but I'm I'm triming the bushes
over here
no there's a buttons down here oh all
that button
work how do you get blue
back that's actually kind of
impressive I'm going to guess there's
more buttons around
here oh okay we
found no you absolute toxicity what I
thought we had
rules did you see that it was like
perfectly timed there was I can't
believe there was no way I was ever
going to be able to recreate that you
that was yours
essentially oh my
God
toxicity competitive gameplay come on
we're
going um you're seeing that what is that
that's a gross cockroach looking thing
I think we need one more person over
[Music]
here just don't leave it back there
that's not a all
right it's like in a different
resolution too do you see
it oh yeah it's just a
jpig well I mean it's a Sprite but like
it's in a higher resolution than the
other thing it's really
unusual I think we need bombs
I think so too but I haven't seen
yet okay so if you imately sword after a
roll you instantly do a
um yeah I can't do damage to it yeah it
doesn't the hammer works
either have to like crush it with these
WS
[Music]
that's
second wait
[Music]
for come
on we just wait does it
roll no oh oh look at
that
dang yeah the controls are weird cuz
like you can just grab onto it and just
um yeah and he take great damage too
like of
course to the
left that was a huge
room do you
[Music]
mind AB some
toxic oh I'm rich
this tingle okay tingle's looking like
the um tingles looking like a little
possessed demon over there I don't think
tingle he's always a
little unusual
[Music]
it's so weird that it's only the guy
who's like um you're controlling
currently how is it that like
[Music]
H I guess
oops I didn't even even want to do that
either yeah I see what we got to do we
need to Mo
[Music]
log there he goes what' you
get he's Rich I'll let you get the other
one I bet you that's power
[Applause]
bracelet how much you want to bet that's
the power nope it's just money even more
money than the last
time NOP
you'll get it I believe wow okay oh I
got the big screen you can
just really goof that
[Music]
one dang kill them both instantly he's a
rich we got something to P out over here
[Music]
oh like ended it for some
reason you got to really hold that
button down and these are just straight
up J pigs you
know a little broken on my own too
[Music]
we got this
log we got to get this lock
first iOS we get across the
holes where you
going there was more down yeah it's the
getting back out
rout is it
W
[Music]
just any day now oh well there he
goes that was the cave you were just
in well you can't get back easily unless
you go all the way
yep all righty boy come on over here
help your old man out help him out with
his if there's not more than wood over
here you see that I can
think all right see that only makes
sense if it's the morning and it's it's
just
not well I don't know if what good that
does us
but you were waiting on it so you seemed
convinced it did
something oh is this like way
back I think it
is like now we what now we got to do
toxic competitor oh there's money in
this
guy I hope you get
money and bestow upon you because of the
toxic flavor base that is only one other
dude we give you money Chuck Ching Chuck
ching and I think now we got to go like
that oh okay red comes back back the
moment we do that
thought okay
maybe maybe one of us goes down
here look at
[Music]
that but there's nothing down
there this like led up
somewhere nope lead where do
this oh okay okay well let's go back
there's another way over here hold on
there's one more thing on this side yeah
like I could have sworn I seen that same
passage way somewhere yeah there's
another one there was another
passageway wait there's a chest we never
been here
before we never been here before like
where is this how do we get
here we just went down here we
go strange we can't actually get in
there
what I tried to throw him purple in
there like a thousand
times you going to have
red how do we miss this area hey I can't
believe you're with all those monsters
around oh you talking what you guys
say but the problem is that I can't even
get to the shed where all our weapons
are store uh who knows since I don't
mind going outside oh can you slay all
those oneeyed monsters
if you do you can use whatever you want
from the storage shed sure I'll say the
monsters really sweet there is lots of
weapons and stuff in the swords that I'm
sure you'll find it good for them uh
take whatever you want just get rid of
all of them one it
monsters like a derogatory but all right
we don't even know here's the key to the
storage shed ah shoot key hell yeah all
right where we use this
key probably down here where the storage
says um this a
[Music]
bomb all right but well there was a
switch over here it's under the
grass well unfortunately I'm on fire
forever
apparently there we go found
it where that open see uh the
door what door none of these Sprites are
working the way out it opened up the way
out oh
okay cuz apparently that was just a
suicide
room what's down
[Music]
there nothing youed
it definitely not me earlier it was all
you I guess this is a puzzle you got all
pull one out so oh we got to pull it
out hold on I'm
coming is that the top of the screen we
might just have to pull it from the
side oh cool didn't know we could do
that wow money chucking so anyways
what's that sword [ __ ] how we kill oh
here it
is I think we were supposed to do this a
while ago is there supposed to be like a
weapon heck yeah I got a
boost did you have a boomerang yeah yeah
you did Boomerang
[Music]
didn't how the heck do we kill these
guys
so I know the hammer doesn't work
on just un calling for Unnecessary
damage to
allies oh shoot there was money in this
tree
[Music]
so much for all kinds of
weapons there was a there was one kind
of weapon you want to try and getting
whatever's underneath this
[Music]
log maybe we have to throw the log on
him
why why are we going in why are you
still holding me I mean I know you care
but thought that refresh it I guess we
just have to go to the next area wait
where' it go oh that's up there can we
walk with a log or is it just Auto throw
it it's uh basically Auto throw ah it's
gone so we probably W use
[Music]
it we heal
up how oh that that wasn't a l
[Music]
before man that's a big one over
there ah there's money in this tree
so we can move
them I guess let's go down one more
[Music]
time and to the left I don't know what's
below us let's check what's below
quick know we came down from
here anything think we can do with the
Pegasus boots that that was a for
area I'll put up road signs up someone's
store room then to the left then go up
to the strange Cade and then go to the
left all right let's follow the path up
in
left then up
again left there's a
left oh there's money in there
you stole my M the from the tree that I
hit as I said my eyes laid claim to it
even even if it uh was already picked up
by me claimed by
me all righty you the
one F the
gy anything in here
all right what's the deal here where are
we supposed to go let's see if there's
anything in
here hey look at that
log may we try picking it
up H yeah we can try just in
case can we move dang look at them Wind
Waker effects being blasted in our face
teasing us with a multiplayer Wind Waker
they'll never make it's going to take
modders and 30 years before they even
get something like going on it'll never
happen I've never seen moders do a
proper implementation of any multiplayer
game the best I've ever seen is like New
Vegas we know how that work I I didn't
mean to fall I was trying
to now it's me waiting on
you all right so what are we supposed to
be doing here I don't know what that
does can't run across a game
we can't run across it right I don't
think
so can you smash those in the
wall I guess not can we
like try to grab
[Music]
I
don't understand
this now we do bounce back up to three
blocks something I don't think our
height changes
though kind of looks
[Music]
that's not
enough I mean what would even get us
across I don't even know if we can jump
that far no I I what to do here cuz all
usually all the things are
self-contained to the area so it's not
like we should have to backtrack for any
of that well that's not true cuz we've
had to backtrack a bit On The Puzzle
level before well that was like
yeah this is obviously one The Puzzle
level is here but let's go back there's
something there was the big log as the
only thing I can think of is somehow we
can deal with that yeah let's see if we
can pick it
up I think the whole reason it's big is
to show that we can't pick it
up wow okay
sure not all at once now but
oh
shoot look I got a big
fairy he pushed
me I'm standing still how can I push
[Music]
you I can even run over holes now that's
pretty
cool oh I guess I guess that's what
we've been eating this whole
time yeah that do
it now the question is can we kill the
eye
guys there was money in here left on the
table
you're
welcome waiting on
me
um can we H him
nope so like do we agree to kill all the
eye guys and we're just going to leave
them now I think that's the whole
premise is that we're trying to do that
is the next thing that's going to get us
through the the level all right so let's
go back over to the spot and then go
pull the log again because we'll need to
do that no we don't we oh yeah do at
least we want to pull this lock again I
not sure why that one stay
out it is kind of that it needs all of
us for that
[Music]
just like think she up on we're good
here right yeah so pretty
straightforward oh there's a
dude you have to use a boomerang
[Music]
wow really hit me for
huh what is that really you're so toxic
I'm just trying to go and move
around don't do it don't do it down that
hole
that's just how the game is played and
I'm just moving around the
field why is there
competitive like oh did you bring the
key you were the key holder what are you
asking me for I don't even know where
the key is I found the
key oh it's a new key
okay thought we got one earlier yeah we
did we did for the
storage all righty let me get this door
open
open there I go oh there's money in the
door a shoot there's a looks like old
grave okay there's water well don't get
rid of the
water yeah okay don't get rid of the
water he say
um I was pushing the wrong
[Music]
button know what to do though
you do yeah let's go back
to no there was that ey in that one area
back to
the well oh so we can get the power Bell
so you
[Applause]
can all right can you shoot that yeah I
can did it do
anything yeah get this to the next area
well I
guess this is how they stop me from
getting to oh no we can't still get out
here
but wait I have to have it to get
that
dang wait can I carry you and run does
this get rid of wait can this s lock us
I don't think so we do we just s lock
ourselves no cuz I put my boot where the
old bow is but in order for me to get
back I need to grab the boot again I
think it's fine cuz I don't think we're
coming back here we're not coming back
here this is the one way for you no we
we got to go back and hit that eye
oh no okay I hit the eyes of the eye
guys okay so that was probably just a
super
okay
hurt now let's go find the
theory which I already forgot
what I have no reason to go in here but
I know you don't there you go
all right you're doing all the heavy
lifting
so got the friendly fire bow watch as it
shoots in every
direction it even shoots him when he's
not
[Music]
looking all right got firing squad
here wow the noise this tingle makes
this gu's are really good
at okay so like now he doesn't want to
look over all right look at
that I thought it said that shoots in
three directions why isn't it shoot in
three
directions wait how how long can you
hold
it
forever all
right
let's toxic I didn't do anything all
right there was an implication of
something the it never
happened therefore no toxicity
occurred you see that wow now that is T
we had an
agreement come back
here is so
terrible how you sto of my people here
get out of here get out of
here why can't I throw you in
there oh oh there's a log here look
you're the toxic one I'm just trying to
get we need to get this log
open
sure [ __ ] this
log there's a log see this that log has
something good for me oh but it's got
It's got something good for me though
yeah therefore we can skip come on come
here there's come on let's go get the
get this get this
log let's see what's in
here oh man he got more Hearts Let's see
that was so good for you you you got the
hearts this is not a combat
fight but that's the literal goal right
now is to do the combat with the light
monsters they are the most passive
creature in this game we're not fighting
like trolls where they'll like shake you
for all your
money wow I really can't believe you're
being so T we had an agreement
[Music]
today not believe this wait did we get
them
off it did do like the little sound we
go back talk to the other guys I think
so
why does that affect me that is a very
good
question what's that you said you you
destroyed all the onee monsters that's
great thank you I really should reward
you um gee what can I give you uh you
headed to the castle huh oh I know
there's this giant tree that blocking
the path to the castle but I dug a huge
passageway so I can get uh into the
castle once I was done with it I sealed
it up but you can dig it open if you
want it here take this shovel in
exchange for the help and you can dig it
up there's a spot north of the shed
where there might be an underground cave
you should start digging in there and
try to find
it if you have a hard time finding it
try going to the great Fair's Fountain
the fairy can make this shovel powerful
shovel oh what I can make a a super
shovel for one thing could you imagine
like action to do all right where's the
fairy again oh we got to get the super
shovel we got it you know what you want
you know you want toxic ass
gaml he goes
wow let me agid your way
super shovel level two shovel find soft
so and dig who knows what you'll find
there's a treasure the Hound
[Music]
around what are you
doing come
on what are you doing come on
[Music]
all right I'll dig right where I'm
standing dang that was supposed to be
it weren't you supposed to have like a
super shovel wait hold on go back up
here real quick did it say north of the
shed do it mean that north of the shed
oh that's pretty neat toxic as
gameplay I only respond to what's given
to
me it's like based on like the amount
that you did it's
interesting
Dam oh this isn't even it this is
garbage this is completely worthless I
need the big gym I got to steal the I
mean I've got to procure the big gym
through all the group
work you can't stop
me you got to dig
[Laughter]
it so stupid
oh found
it ah what is
this wow that that actually had
nothing oh what how did I fall down
again I me definitely wasn't the three
pushing me
in yeah that one
tracks wow okay
dang come on you're usually good at
picking the right one wa the first time
what's going on
today hold down the
Dig why did you upgrade to the super
shovel and then just never hold it down
what do you mean hold it down holding
down doesn't do anything oh thought the
hold down was supposed to like make you
dig in a 2 by two or
something I'm holding the
button that's what he was like he's like
get the fair upgrade if you need help
how's it's basically a
Pathfinder oh as in like the sound
effect close you in yeah
okay there's something down
here I think it's in this
[Music]
area no
walk over
here yeah there's a hole in this
[Music]
[Applause]
are you know want this
yeah Dam it was NAB an empty
box no how was that not it
I can't believe
this unless it's not in this area do we
need to go
up say north of the shed can't go up
there I think I found something
[Music]
I think you just missed it back
here yeah see there's still the signal
so there's still a hole over
here it's like right here
[Music]
I mean that's fine don't choose
[Applause]
I'm
F got to get the gym
first toxic
gaml there was no toxicity in that that
was a Fair Race you even jump down the
hole first I did all that shoveling you
only call it to well yeah you're the one
with a shovel you there's only one
shovel in this
level is that supposed to me you're just
jealous because I'm in first place for
the first time and you can't handle it
struggling to
Coast although you know there's more
level to be had I can I can willingly
give you first place
[Music]
where you finding the else uh
feather
oh how what is this
going oh that's
interesting oh that's you yeah it'd be
great if I wasn't blending in with the
enemies was
like why is this one so separated
what' you get there I'll take
money and bomb that would have been
would have been useful a few minutes ago
very helpful a few minutes
[Music]
ago oh can I use it here to insta kill
so um I don't know
I feel like you should probably save it
for the boss I want to see if it works
the
ball that's a moon
Pearl no my
Medallion a
man you just had to throw it
down no I I put it down didn't throw it
that was the
issue this guy's actually going to kill
me
kill easily that's pretty
good
madallion no link grab The Medallion yo
Bros it's me what is this it's like they
took another Sprite and pasted it on top
of it it literally looks like an RPG
Maker
Sprite the of high Ru I mean the Knight
of Hyrule charged with guarding the blue
Royal
Jewel to my shame I fell under the the
sway of some other dude's
Swagger and the transformed into a basic
creature of magic a swagless skippity
list rless creature the jewel was also
cursed and it became a portal to the
Dark World you got to say those you got
to say the lines from the kiddos you
know it's going to be cringe in like 5
years but yeah really dating the video
you're done right I'm sorry for the for
for the citizens of hyal who suffer and
the Princess
Zelda uh yeah it's roughly what you see
I trust you're going into the realm of
the heavens and and the Palace of wind
however hum must first gather the Royal
jewels that reveal the path towards like
did this did the story change all of a
sudden like we literally like get this
like side quest it's like um we need you
to suddenly change the games you're
going after Jewels now well the basic
gist is that this guy failed at his job
now he's pushing all the work onto us so
just just like real
work except for in his case he's he's um
talking to us from you know the slack
that involves the people who've been
fired that's interesting you do are you
the one doing this I thought I had
control of this uh bro there are three
other Guardian Knights I Fe they had too
been charged changed uh free free them
from the dark curse and retrieve the
jewels the lights like Seth Rogan
it could be you want it to be how you're
not dead yet I see that quarter heart
you still got you're like you're about
to trip on like a like a twig this die
poke your eye out the light must return
to hyru I entrust you with the blue
Jewel and with it I have place in your
hands the the the sheer hopes wishes and
dreams of all
Hyrule I added to that one I thought
that was a little more
impactful okay no Medallion we took too
long in a
dialogue W I can't believe this we could
really use that to this uh for this wind
T oh it just comes back okay that's cool
no link The Medallion link
no blue fying saucer why is it Blue Link
none of us were playing blue
rink I think you were weren't you
no I was so red you you had all the
whole time that was only red yeah I know
I'm a little confused by it too oh man
there's the side quest oh look at that I
get a thing oh awesome I can't move yet
it's not fair my
Medallion I I just literally cannot move
really
yeah you hear me uh pressing buttons
there your controller get unplugged you
die what's wrong with
you no the controller's working
I know pick me up maybe it'll fix it in
the next
area my Medallion how I it for so long
and you wasted
[Music]
it no I still can't
move how did that cut scene break my
movement you don't have to can jump over
it you can just hit them yourself s
for you don't even need me for this part
put me put me down out of the
lightning I could do with the Swagger of
the blue
Knight got to make every last one count
you
know I got to drag your butt over here
has to be
done I'm not a willing participant in
losing my controls
nice put me on the green yeah what's uh
what's up with your
controls like I said the controller
seems to be working fine so something
wrong with the game oh my my dignity my
one thing I'm actually competitively
entice the work
with lost when did it start Counting
Hearts remaining always been counting we
just like hardly ever lost
any see like it wouldn't this this P
part here doesn't matter because you you
already know your count before you do
the final part it's probably a little
less obvious when you have four people
and you're not keeping track of
anything like you have again I
have enough to beat you ooh look at that
number one smoke D why' you even bother
getting any gems this whole
time if only I hadn't done all that
digging uh we might actually need to
restart the game I don't let me see can
I move on the menu let me see if I can
move
here yeah I need you to save for us
we'll
restart that's pretty cool didn't know
you could just lose your uh controls
like that
which means they going have to do like
the
whole wait what did you do that no this
is I have controls now that's neat how'd
you do that literally did nothing he did
absolutely nothing and still
won oh dude it's a swamp level hey
what's up Bros I've come to give you
some more
information be cautious link a poisonous
swamp lies ahead vti I curse the name
his actions have poisoned the very land
the creatures who lived here have long
since fled the effects of the his foul
presence Now All That Remains are
monsters and floating weeds that lead
Travelers
astray believe you can vinish his this
foulness and return High rule to its
former Beauty link my friend take care
not to get lost and drowned in this
poisonous swamp I feel
like who who's
like who's drinking the swamp water to
verify it's poisonous
the color of the swamp looks
poisonous don't touch
it I'm
rich that's crazy I went through all
that effort to get that 100 and they
just give you one for killing like the
dumbest creature in the game that
dumbest creature actually has ability to
defend
itself I mean the one ey monsters is
literally just like
big they're just big and move
around it's bro
again bro got places to be how are you
going to call him a after he does that
it's
crazy I guess there must be something
good here trying to
hide I didn't make it can
see I got absolutely
annihilated I think I get what we need
to do
it's like waiting killing waiting the
video
game a no they tricked me my greed
wasn't greedy
enough dang these bats are like actually
kind of messing
up wow I like how when I get it from a
monster you see this you see this here
on the screen see this that's what
happens when I
do ah I didn't get a door fast
enough don't worry I'll still the rules
of not
taking wait could I didn't know where I
was no tingle tingle Tingle take it oh
my God tingle the
toxicity tingle's a little son of a
toxic like
that why does this bro has so many bombs
where do he get tier three bomb from
what Great Fairy out there is like yeah
tier free bombs for
you dark Great
Fairy this is the junest ladder on the
planet
here I see how they did the ladder I
it's pretty obvious it's just another
tile that you can walk
on literally no restrictions to like
left or right or
anything doing
that no my
heart there we go
toxic walks into a dude throwing a
boulder just in case you lost your
[Music]
last they can roll up a
ladder do we like jump up here nope
that's pretty
cool love that
do you I'm trying to get this thing
killed I me if you're like yeah I don't
mind killing me but all
right oh I see I get it
[Music]
yeah you needed
that I can watch you on the big
screen with my Game Boy
SP where you going
I'm obviously having control issues
here oh when it came back the controls
died as
[Music]
well no I didn't lose control I was just
mixing up buttons as it was my fault the
sign
says tingle time tingle got stuck in
icky sludge it is so slimy tingle must
write all this down so that the same
thing doesn't happen next time I will
gracefully uh flit um from Leaf to Handy
Leaf jumping of such Joy almost skipping
from Zora to
Zora what is this a what how did I go in
the
lava D we destroyed that bird we're like
no we're not doing with you anymore
we've had enough of your fun you see
this Jun this is what happens when I try
to kill
him there's a way to do it that
a so
close it's
garbage oh okay sure
dang oh I need I need some hearts you
know what there might be something in
this grass over here hold on there's not
anything grass oh there's another heart
in
here you didn't even need time what's
your excuse now potentially dying
later this
disappear oh there's door on
them dang I timed it
wrong get out of
here oh okay you don't have to actually
jump
okay but you do have to be prepared to
move
remember a kid
game I did
so blue was on there L still that's
crazy okay even though we're way up
there you still can't
go wait what's going on
here oops okay I might actually
[Music]
die what did you do I couldn't move
anymore there's that much I can do for
you on this
one what are these
do gives you money I
guess
let's come on what are you doing you
don't no no no you don't you don't need
that no no no do money Mone money CH
chain
money okay
oh I'm
the button oh there's more of now oh
there's there's no there's less of them
now it's time for purple's time to shine
wait I can't do anything
here do you have to unlock it
first how do I get how did I suddenly
get bad at
[Music]
this the real answer is you've been bad
all
lot there you go
dang imagine being like red or purple
right
now how did I get jumped out of that
one Welcome to my
life I see a cave I go in it
hey I
gotc finally some
heals hey and there's money in
here wait how do I get
[Music]
back um I guess I was supposed to go
this way you got to jump a little more
oh
yeah you know I appreciate that they
actually did get rid of like the damage
sound after a little
bit probably cuz they realized the
testers were complaining about it yeah
but like every other zeld game never did
that just saying I appreciate
it and by every other Zelda I mean we
didn't in like two zeldas
so I had really played very
many oh I got to play on the big
screen yeah you're you're the slow poke
this
[Music]
done there's a boo in this
game I can be hurt by a
sword oh you push him
I had money of mine what did you get you
got
puzzle nothing yet I think we fall on oh
no there's a dark world we need
a I think we need to oh there's a dude
in
mine oh no this just works okay oh it's
a teleporter never
mind I I don't want in this though back
[Music]
out oh no I found money in
M yeah I found guess what does my screen
look like in the bottom
left
um
nothing
uhoh uhoh um oh okay here we go that's
fine the giant skull or something else
that's for sure oh a bat that
whoa that's like a vampire
bat I hit it once got
faster okay I get it well you said like
No Stealing the the gyms those are tiny
ones I think you have blatantly
disregarded every rule we've set down
this I have followed them greatly yeah
multiple
times that's countable the number of
times I follow the
rules no I'm just getting I guess we go
up those are tiny gems I don't really
care honestly I don't really care much
about the gems
anyway it's a meme I pay more lip
service than I actually feel
about is this a person now they're dead
they dead again
what they
say they're
scared I'm scared I think I died and
there's others there's others that died
as
well what are these like what are these
tiles they like tiny tombstones or
something I guess stone
walls I see let's go
down oh okay same area
oh is
it wait do we go to the left oh
no no I mean there was an area up top
right I just thought this is a different
area oh you're
right some of these Maps do be kind of
confusing but take my hope for
what'd you
get nothing just healed me garbage fairy
man got the fairy of garbage you're the
fairy of
garbage you know I work really hard kid
and all you do is insult
me do we need to go back for the the bow
now I know where the bow is I just don't
know how to lock
it guess let's go back for the bow oh
you want to be the Bowman this
time jumping's pretty
fun yeah it's up to you you tell
me you like trolling with that thing
what do you think the the purpose of
asking you
is where was the
bow this way I
[Applause]
think and yet it's still not
unlocked wait how do I get back
you just jump back oh once you shoot the
eyes you'll be able to get path
back where was the big stalos that's
probably where we have to go it was in
that one above
it up here yeah it was in that
one I already killed him
though oh fig that have something to do
with it oh shoot we missed something
what did we miss
what were the other one I didn't check
them all oh those was just like mostly
empty rooms and chests like
[Music]
that what do you
think we got to get rid of the stones
you slow my
heart so
toxic yeah there could be something down
there something
more looked like if you jumped up into
the right it was
more no I guess not
actually now that you're here it's a lot
easier to like see if I'm actually
moving I think it's it I think this is a
pit wait why did I fall back in no I I
stepped on something here there's
more I thought there was
one there's not
[Music]
okay
so okay sure than and there he goes
again all right let's see here maybe
there was more tombs up
north yeah we tried those
right can't kill her sure we miss
anything over here
[Music]
yeah maybe one of these we have to
move oh she just heals
you and the center one we need the bow
for
right yeah
I don't get it something needs to be
done to get
that wait you have full health don't we
no we don't have the uh the slashy sword
yet the the beam sword we need need like
a thousand more gems or something
well we missed something
somewhere
oh
what the people there another
person like okay sure we know that we
need a gym for that or Jewel oh we can
go up there
nice yeah but how
that girl is um sure having
some yep definitely not a creepy pasta
you know looking demonic
creature May if I jump and throw Blue
Link at the perfect time oh you can't
throw when you're in no you can
hang on you has to be separate
though you has to be
separate you're still one
unit okay then you do it what do you
mean you're you're already attempted to
do
it I don't think you can go that far
dang I missed I hit the attack button
instead of the oh no I think the poison
got the green link oh no
ah dang it's hard to like time that
one yeah you get like no time even if
you're in the
air in fact I think the moment I throw
them is the moment I instantly snap
down so I think they might
that all right let's try something south
of the swamp
serves your right slashing me like that
I'll slashing the
grass so I can get some uh precious
Hearts oh there something we had to have
missed what is
this I feel like this isn't
involv pretty sure it's just North
somewhere we're missing something
here the hearts have given up on being
hearts and you didn't you didn't get
anything from
it's like we need bombs or
something ah there we go figured it out
oh what was it there was a button yep
there was a button underneath the
pot all right get your bow let's
go wait how do I get out of here then
shoot the eye and make a path I thought
I already said that earlier didn't I
wait how do I get out of here
you'll figure it
out here's only a little special on
Friday
nights do you mind you don't need to
roll that last time
you you you
monster you're trying so hard do you
[Music]
mind oh my
no no no you don't even get the
option oh
man look at me group project over
here you see that Dark Souls
Dodge they will be measuring up in the
dark souls for days
[Music]
I need you to come over here with the
rock
feather you sure yeah
[Music]
this like a two-player only secret have
a only single player you won't be able
to do
it what that
do he's a rich
over here getting us the power what have
you been doing this whole time hitting
switches set them free ah of course the
last
[Music]
one looks like it's up to
you why did that bat sound like a
monkey oh I didn't make you
jump nothing
like just get in there and shoot it it's
proximity
based oh you're like Invincible while
you're
doing that was so weird
I think you're supposed to hit that one
cuz you can
jump yeah I can't hit
that you never hit them with the you're
supposed to hit that you never hit them
with the the sword though but I can't
how am I supposed to do it yeah like a
special
let's see no no but how much supposed
get over
there use your
brain I know what the solution is but
don't worry I'll let
you it is simple we've done it a million
times all right now I definitely can't
get
that just throw one of your guys over
there come on
man make me make me do it it like this I
do I wanted to spare you the shame of
you know me telling you you could have
just like got me over there or something
or carried me or
whatever I no you just had to walk away
like ah God forbid I do some of the
work you got it I believe in
you it goes down
D I'm just robbing
Everything feels
good to be fair I am taking more damage
than oh I got this
thing okay we know where to bring it at
least that's really far away
though it wouldn't be an escort Quest
without
it escort the Pearl they
said you'll do just fine they
said even memorize the path that I'm
pretty good with
that give me a minute you'll never find
it you'll never find
it it's not there it doesn't exist it's
not real
dang it's red
only you see this Prejudice they're
doing here it's all right it says the
guy who just robbed the whole
graveyard and yet my wealth is only like
what is this like 16 above
you the
real I need you over here okay well how
do I get over there this is red
only do I throw you or
something maybe you do something in
there while you're over there unlock oh
it's stampe look at him look at his
marvelous he looks like a 10 oh shoot I
got a thing I've got the power bracelet
I can Fuel and lift anything I can lift
dampe n he's still too big T it's
dangerous out there you shouldn't be
wandering around this shadow guy has
been stif stirring up trouble lately
actually he looks like you but of course
he's not you he's that cool like you are
my name was damp I'm supposed to be the
caretaker of this graveyard oh the do
that again I want to see that on the big
screen I want to see on the big screen I
want to see on the big
screen there like one you see this
there's like one tiny spot I have to
stay in these creatures are so these
creatures are so pleased they treat our
world like their own new home listen up
boys Legend speaks of a mirror in which
a dark tribe was sealed away long ago it
uh I understand it's supposed to be
hidden now somewhere in the dark on the
forest of light the forest's been
covered by pitch black clouds recently
it's the forest of dark now yep no
mistake about it something bad to breu
there all right good old Dume with his
like three-hour exposition
all right so I need you to need you to
like catch all that on fire I
guess wait come over here again I can't
now come up to the tree can I
like we grabing that
although I'm curious come come further
down further down can I grab you you can
grab
me yeah ah dang it it's so
silly oh that's what you do duh what
just grab me and drag me across the the
poison
oh see they should have been uh
I had to I had to do it rebelling
against this this toxicity had to do
it no to be fair I would have done the
same that was funny
wait why did I going back in it no stop
that's
embarrassing you see this guy he just
dived right back into the Dark World
right after he comes out of
it a they're
Invincible got K on the Flames
[Music]
first I need something for all that hard
work I just did what do you mean I'm the
one who solved the puzzle for you
wait did he say
anything oh yeah what does he
[Music]
say n it's dangerous I'll take this with
you in like hands of something sure he
just uh he just hands you his dignity
and Life Choices hands the grappling
hook that' be nice okay what was over
here was this a dead
end whoa
okay I didn't know you could do that I'm
I'm jacked right now can you pick up
this rock though no right here no really
you tried yeah it's on the stream I got
it
recorded pretty embarrassing
man I get the feeling we're not supposed
to be in the
spotlight I don't know what tells me
that but like you know getting that
feeling why can't I grab
this oh light's coming
did you get down
there oh there's a dude here I came to
visit my departed wife's grave and since
she showed up always got money uh she
came to visit my grave I wish someone
would don't break the pots they can
hear I wish someone because you're
because you're in the dialogue it's not
doing anything
a and oh I'm impacted now because of
[Music]
that it's really just an opportunity you
see okay come over here real quick I
need you to get these off sorry I need
you to get these off
me get it off of you what do you
mean uh okay I guess this is just a
thing now
can we go back reset
it wait there was a tree
there oh yeah you're right do
mind that's kind of wild I just
look then it's like yeah let's add
Friendly Fire to the that's a
really I'll never forgive these game
developers
oh my job's
[Music]
done any day down
me oh it's the boss from uh Wind
Waker I've never seen this seen before
they never seen this boss before some
Wind Waker I never played Wind Waker
[Music]
we have no idea
who's so like we have someone stand on
here and hit him or
something looks like it how did you kill
him Winder um you put light on
him oh I hit
him you played one weaker really
yeah I mean with your legal with your
legal um Nintendo console you should
definitely play
one why would I
want good
game you got to kill him you got to kill
the little
guy how's too busy picking up
gems that is more important we all know
this is
true I need
I need to put you to shame when I get
first place
again see I'll hit two of them at
once dang that's not right that's not
right at all how could they just put in
300 at the end you still You Still
Smoked
me even with that Gap closed You Still
Smoked me you notice that when we reduce
the toxicity I'm more likely to
win you
it you trying to say you're some kind of
better gamer when little the playing
field is
leveled think was died
oh never mind never mind I hit by those
moms at the beginning of the level
remember oh yeah that's really about
that yeah I didn't stand a chance I
needed that 300 that was a that was a
Pity 300 you didn't need it I needed
that to solidify my victory even more
that doesn't make a bit of sense at all
he's
lck as the richest of the two of us I
need more money you see you don't need
any money you don't have enough to do
anything with it so you might as well
just give it to
me what is this logic wouldn't I just
need more money so I can continue
surviving with the littles that I do
have doesn't make any
sense you can't do anything with the
money it's better in my
hands yeah sure take that yeah what do
you
got show us what you got for us today
what what garbage competitive
Cooperative
competitive competiti
competitive competitive Whopper
competitive don't
Whoppers Monster hunting I like this
game they just force you to walk over
here they just
like fancy tingle timer tingle's a tad
upset about all the monsters appearing
hereabouts you're going to kick the
Beast around a bit you have to force
fairies and no
whining I don't I don't know why I give
him like a a list thereally
accent not not it's not right she from
those
people so like it's just
kill
[Music]
die oh nice extra 100 but it say killed
more monsters though
wait why did I why did I lose it oh did
these guys drop
Hearts I mean I kind of dig the concept
of this you know it's not bad compared
to the other ones where it's like put a
chicken in a cave that's like one of the
worst Zelda missions in oaring of
time at least this one's like you know
there's something to
[Music]
it wait what are these things down
here
yeah oh what are those things down
there I guess they're bats no they're
the vultures
[Music]
oh my God think to kill us oh that's
just
you dang look at all these
gems I mean like I said it's an
interesting
concept I guess this would be well this
is still the
uh game cubes this isn't too out of the
ordinary for the
like number of Sprites you know
yeah you didn't even kill this
one what did I die
from see how like half your
gym oh no not those guys get no he's on
top of me
can we shoot him at least we can't shoot
him
[Music]
dang oh my god get off of
me why is it so
brutal why do they take so much
damage oh my God this is this is
actually ridiculous what the the
heck oh you got to kill so many of them
too good Lord wow that's a challenge and
a
half I mean I get the I get I get what
we got to do now but like dang that's
that's really
tough why yours drop a blue that doesn't
seem
fair uh I guess he was a special
one you going to
die I mean it's tell us to go up so s
get the hard
you'll get a force gem for each batt you
defeated cool oh wow you really smoked
them and yet you still won because of
your
greed it was my it's my compliment prize
my my complimentary prize for
participating in the other uh losing uh
aspects so let me revise my opinion of
that mini game it's a very cool concept
but there shouldn't be any Force gems
involved
that ruin these FL gyms are ruining
everything get rid of
them we doing one more level yeah we can
do one
more oh it's night I like this I like
this music it's good
mus it's really quiet
onun it's like the music's much quieter
in the sound effects
what are these fairies for again uh in
case we die those are our lives
well you do now come
on don't oh my God why did you do
that oh my what have you done can I like
claim I'm not I'm not with you
you look like
me doesn't matter I'm with I'm with
schmuck do you like go of me oh my God
the toxicity let go of me what are you
doing so
toxic oh we can't even get in there
anyways dang
[Music]
yeah I don't think there's anything we
can do to get up
[Music]
there oh wait maybe May
oh it's so close
though they've got to have like timed
this right oh I did
it garbage I got get rid of these Force
gems and move them don't need
him okay I'm back to the game what are
we
doing how'd you get down
there I got good
can you hit it through the wall I'm
curious
nope 10 out of 10 gameplay would play
again dude that's crazy the like mind
power you're doing to sustain
that I think it's just perfectly off
sync
looks like it
was you want the hammer yeah I haven't I
haven't done the
hammer plus you're a little more toxic
with the uh the boomerang so uh okay
let's uh let's look back last episode
but I had the bow and
arrow not the last uh oh why do you keep
doing you got me call oh can I claim
that I'm not with you
like like since they don't even bother
putting the another lock on door dang I
got scammed
again stop breaking the door pots but
it's so
so I got to carry his sorry sorry son of
a gun
ask if I don't oh yeah it's really right
here what you do you didn't even open
I'm going steal I'm going steal purple
there's a solo for
me it was worth
it toxic gameplay okay but to be fair
those lights are on
you go got to
keep I got purple back
apparently oh yeah that's interesting
how that
happened do it just like reset you to be
base how did I grab
you dude I tell you if I ever need to
grab you I know
how why you
keep
why Dy yall are even perfectly alive
when you get hit
this is so
ridiculous no it's like takes the
priority I think to grab
you let's prove this Theory let's
see there you
[Music]
go you just have the whole group now
there you go the solo project for me
again I got to have I got to have how
did you grab me when I'm rolling down
the thing like don't ask how did you to
grab you half the time you were trying
to get blue
so the last me look at these water
effects
fany we got these one Wier water effects
greed on this say the guy who picked up
the
oops you had just had to be drowning
here we go
again oh boy here we go again why is
there always a red junor you can get so
many Force just yeah you can just uh
scum
it okay this time for real this time
it gave you purple again I I'm not
anybody and neither are
you what do your characters show up on
your end cuz the characters don't show
up my end yeah got maybe we'll change
them go under water and come back
up interesting I have like little like
sailboats well we are in the water oh
they fixed
oh
dang are they going to actually do
anything about it they don't even care
oh nice
save can you can you get rid of that bat
with a boomerang use the Boomerang on
it has still to be like horizontal oh
dang that was worth don't move they
don't if you're if you're standing like
a statue you're good to go it's dinosaur
oh I
forgot the like monkey brain of me it's
like o pot must
break and uh you're going to give me
grief for
it lizard says happy pot must break
monkey says number go
big I have check this
out damn no one
found I was I was a I was hting a but I
think I needed to
hit Buton
oops okay okay okay this time for real
I'll stop screw us over
no denial of service attack those were
mind hold on let me yeah I was hitting
the wrong button God dang
it I mean there's only two buttons how
hard can it be
exactly we never did go that way can we
I guess
not maybe if we're in line that was
good trying to be slick me this
[Music]
time but I mean infinite Force GS let's
be real I am the group project now you
stole him how could you you stole him he
was me my myself and I and so are you
myself and I
oh I almost forgot I H A
again dang almost got
me I think we can go this way I'm going
if we long come over here
wow you really got caught on purpose
just so I could I did not get caught on
purpose uhuh that's what that's they all
say we'll get through this one day this
is going to be the longest level of all
it's like stupid mistakes too is not
even
I again hit the wrong button at this
point it's just like smash both buttons
immediately you want to get your gems
again they some
Spa I got to get my uh chest
again should go
back ah I was trying to be slick oh my
God what are you doing there's no need
for that it's a kid's
game how could you take the most okay
actually it's like the red one is random
yeah I thought it was that pot that you
holding
there dang okay mixing it up this
time I got to keep purple on his
toes it gave me blue again yeah what is
this I guess it I guess it is just based
on when we first got C got guess blue is
player three and I got two and
four I'll never get that chest at this R
what are you doing why you hanging
back you're not trying to be toxic with
that are
you come
on oh okay
oh my you are so toxic to you got the
gym my dude what are you complaining the
gym is worthless I had that you got
caught on purpose so I couldn't get that
I did not I cannot believe
you
absolute toxicity that this man is
showing
unreal I don't know what's real anymore
come here not not you purple you don't
need to be associated with this
band competitive game
play
no
Deni that was good I'm done robbing
you okay so there there a little bit of
something going on here
[Applause]
oh oh shoot I was not expecting that I
see they're going based on the wall
so I guess we're going to be getting the
bow here
[Music]
shortly this is a unusual switch you
have to
admit this switch was made for men of
four arms
get
it forearms quicker quicker just
done toxic gameplay you can
gra look at me so generous letting you
keep the temporary
item was it up
there where was it oh okay
here I
go I found the
[Music]
B I guess I want that as well
was there anything else around there
nope
really yeah what is up with this
strange was another pair coming I didn't
want to do that I'm going to miss the
chance to go well I still got hit
anyways
so supposed to be going right now A what
is can't this game think I can still get
up
though okay they're actually pretty
generous with
that did you get
one I hit that and it didn't do anything
oh it's a it's a thing well it's not
time it's that there's an actual path
you get the
key you didn't get that
earlier get what earlier those two
chests yeah there's get
[Music]
to I guess we'll get the feather at some
point no we can do
well you could but I I
can't oh hey it's a good thing you
didn't get that uh uh
uhoh
uhoh got
hit I think if I'm move to the other
tile it'll make me
fall I'm
back cool I always like that Concept in
games use like arrow shoot
through guess do your two up there
I did there I can't do this road because
there's no torch here huh what do we
do what what hit me that was me
[Music]
my wait what what are you doing I have
no
dudes oh I see you can grab
one give me blue it looked like you grab
[Music]
purple oh
h
[Music]
wait what what was it the bottom row oh
I didn't think about bottom
row it's time for me to do the group
project you
sure they'll do it I've got to though
it's a pot
a I didn't think there was one down
below thought I could Escape oh new jail
yeah
cool we're uh coming better
[Music]
in
um do I throw you from further back or
something uh yeah let just go back up
have fun with the group project did it
give me blue again it
did oh your
greed the answer to everything is
uh his greedy nature even when it's say
it's not you
know big brain no greed
okay nothing out here
now I don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
sure sure you don't want one of these
guys what the those are ladders yeah
that was a new ladder
Sprite no no no no don't want
you I think you actually do have to do
that mechanic
now cool okay yeah I dig
it oh dang did you know it was up there
yeah I saw it earlier okay the
one dang
dude I like how I called your greed out
and then yeah there you there you are
with almost double the uh the count I'm
definitely greeting it up this
time it's a curse that passes around
it's like um a thermostat you
know um these two yeah I guess just
these
two okay interesting do you do it guess
I have to stops me from bringing a
[Music]
bow I mean if you had four players two
people could bring it B I
[Music]
guess oh yeah look at that they block
the bow
off they really don't want you have the
bow for
this I guess it it was four player you
could yeah that's what I was
saying I I see though that you
completely IGN head
it's this dude again from Wind Waker the
famous Wind Waker boss it's a different
boss it's the same boss but when Waker
[Music]
B how do you have full
health I got some
hearts all right that really has a
interesting
range there's a heart over here you want
well I can blow you into the uh the
spikes yeah I think that's how he
supposed to damage you cuz it doesn't do
damage otherwise do we just have to like
light them all before we can actually
hit them
yeah and not get caught okay hit
them oh like one hit per go I got
slurped oh
by
gross don't seem to be able to hurt
him is that tingle you're beating on
that's kind
of yeah it's pretty easy if we justat
I got slurped up again this is a very
different way to like view this
boss how is he like in the you like
bombs and miror shield and
stuff well I mean wind wer wasn't a [ __ ]
game so you got to wonder why yeah
that's why it looks so weird like if you
notice like it looks way different than
all the other Sprites
like you have to wonder why they decided
to make a SP this guy so just making a
boss oh no I never been on the outside
before it's literally just
surv why is Tingle trying to avoid me
WR it's like discount
tingle dang but lift purple up how did
you do that how did you do that how is
that even possible did you see
that oh man I just like leled up my
toxicity you're on a different level
now that was incredible I I now know the
strategy like wow just use my dude as a
weapon I just use
my that was completely by accident by
the
way I was just like get rid of this guy
and just
your turn to
read your turn or my turn yeah you you
you're player one right link thank you
you carry my hopes I read the last one
too this is crazy you carry my hopes
with you as well as all of high
[Music]
rules wait is that the blue jewel blue
Royal Jewel you carry how did you come
by
it is that so the Knights of high rule
so even the Jewels are
now link all we can do is put our faith
in the light and press
on overcoming each obstacle that
confronts
us my Forest has lost its light Darkness
covers it like a
[Music]
shroud link will you go to the forest
perhaps you will find some clue there
in the heart of the forest is a temple
the dark mirror can be found
there long ago a dark tribe invaded H
well you can't say that kind of it's
kind of not
right they were defeated and imprisoned
within the
mirror the tribes mirror prison was then
secreted
interesting word choice a way and hidden
in the Forest Temple to sever its
connection to this
world that dark mirror must never fall
into the hands of those with evil
Hearts link the mirror is a danger in
anyone's hands but yours no one else can
be trusted
just keeps going retrieve the dark
mirror from the palace and keep it until
Princess Zelda is
safe
please you are the only one we can
depend
on first let us proceed to the
[Music]
forest there you go how was
that I almost fell asleep on that one me
too I was reading it
[Music]
imagine if textbooks were presented to
you that slowly and you had to read them
like that and you couldn't like go back
you'd be like 80 years old by the time
you finish a
Bachelors no one would be able to get it
into like the Masters because of time
constraints you just literally not be
able
to or the flip side is literally no one
would ever read them
dang look at you always getting the
enemy defeated one it's pretty
good that's not going to be
enough like it only gives me a 300 boost
when you had like a thousand ahead of
me well I guess the idea is again if
you're splitting it between four each
person would only get like
yeah yeah it'd be half I didn't even
come
close dude my greed was on another level
in this one you don't say just keeps
going a thousand
more just shy of a thousand more I
should say let's get this up on like the
thumbnail next
week here we
go oh my Lord he took he took a snapshot
of it if I don't might as well not
exist you like for the first like 10
levels you were beating me like by that
much every single
time we stopping in here we uh doing
another one uh how do you feel about it
I can go one more I think but oh let's
do one more
there W Woods okay link this is the
forest of light or rather it once was
now the darkness grows deep and the air
stagnant I wonder if some clue might
reveal itself
here you did say that AE go it seems
that many foul beasts are gathering here
perhaps you might be able to learn
something from
[Music]
them so are are like the maidens still
like hanging out with us or what yeah
the think they're all supposed to
technically be in our
party oh that was weird like hits you
before you even touch them
near we just just can't hit him without
the
jump well maybe you can hit him cuz he's
only following
me I mean I did try too early did you
not see that oh oh there it is
okay DK starting off with the big
greed that it's no longer money it's no
longer currency it's just a oh no I get
a floor Master got me
oh there's a lot of them what the
heck you left one down here we're up
here yeah looks like we
can we can't swap to
him I'm going to
[Music]
die that's nice of them to not let the
floor Masters get you when you're by the
[Music]
edge looks like it's up for us garbage
pass
[Music]
you got to get you some hearts got give
me some hearts too
what pathways are dead as do we go to
that Dark World area was there something
in
there
the cool
was there a down
pathway uh yeah I don't
know guess
was there's a
sign yo Jimbo tingle times volume Five
Oh everywhere I go Woods Woods even more
Woods Lost Woods everywhere here A
solidary A solitary road sign just for
you Woods Woods Woods Woods perfect
good the heart drop rate is kind of low
on these bushes oh never mind these on
are I guess we purpose oh
oops Yeah I guess we get purposely CAU
here
[Music]
nope not in this
one I'm a dying I'm dying
again wait I don't get to own blue
because because what yeah cuz you you
still own him you you you have property
rights to
blue just a
gold he's just one of
us let's go back for some
hearts no Hearts here s let's go back
for some
hearts the ones actually give us
Hearts didn't think that there would
actually be different drop RS here we
are all right so what are we doing is
this like a path thing that we got to
[Music]
do I will have all of
them did the tingle thing tell us the no
I just said Woods Woods Woods four times
ex exactly well it doesn't look like
we're being teleported so looks at least
like it'll be consistent
oh wow you hit the wrong one
[Music]
oh
cool I guess I'm running feather this
time you can run boots you did get here
[Music]
first plus it looks cool when three guys
jump look at that
fix
[Music]
that wow that yeah sure nope you really
going to do
[Music]
this here we go
[Applause]
what you doing
[Music]
there no I need you as
well we can do this all day if you won't
how did I have the button priority I
have the button priority how do this
player one have the button priority I
have to get used to it now we going this
way we going this way this kind of crazy
can't like shake out of that there's
nothing over oh you can grab me I guess
yeah
[Music]
they're all mine now how about
that I had to do
it the the your your greed was getting
to
me I have had no greed this game look
who has the most
here look at all that greed you got
right now yeah I have 186 versus your
268 you all those players with you
helping you out all those um little
green all those SL getd
this to do
[Music]
this oh you w ready
yet there we go I guess only you can get
it it's not
fair I got this thing
there you go you could have
[Music]
it for a minute there I thought I just
saw
F the Nintendo Game map it's interesting
look at how Blue's got it
[Music]
now didn't think they could grab
items well you got to jump me across
first what oh that's
embarrassing oh if you try to throw it
you instantly snap downward yep yep I
thought I mentioned that earlier when I
is talking about
the no seriously got to take the
girls oh oh I didn't you could kill him
that way that's pretty
cool so we don't even know where this
goes yet do we want to keep going down
south was it further down heck
[Music]
yeah do you know where it was
that's right I have my own toxic
abilities how can I play so uh Frugal
friendly when you're out there toxi it
up we been right
here the answer was
[Music]
no I guess I'm now the torch
guy which means I'm a I'm support
what's that no vti's old news ganon's
the king of Darkness forget
vti how how all I did was push down how
does pushing down do that you can burn
the logs at least so go and
burn crazy you're uh you're looking a
little uh I don't feel so good Mr
Stark oh no
man you just spoiled all of the marble
can't believe
[Music]
this
oh oh shoot whoa he got me
too I wasn't even paying attention
dang okay well to be fair I shouldn't be
stealing your Stu I think we did agree
to that at
least then he got
me I guess
left well no that's just
toxic when I do it it's toxic but when
he does it that's right them's the rules
I I like the bone area I like where
bones are going toxic when you get money
it's not toxic when I get that's called
um true capital
gains what it say I didn't read you
don't see me like running into these
trees de scrub bulletin board if you're
not a deu scrub stop reading now can't
read this not legally
anyways you're done with the key use to
lock the place where like when you're
done with the key use to lock the place
where we hid the shovels be sure to put
it back from where you got it
from that was an
[Music]
interesting here I need you for a moment
clean all these guys
up I think it still gave it to me it
doesn't
matter it doesn't matter when I do it
but of course we you do
[Music]
it yeah what do I do when I give the
torch
[Music]
torch oh she can't do anything for me
call it a torch wait a minute you
British suddenly that's what it says
when you pick it
up or is it said Lantern one or the
other well can't you bust those trees
now no I don't think I think the onlyone
just lets me run over
gaps basically the placement for the
whole
let me get my weapon of mass destruction
over
here how I'm pushing the button I'm
literally pushing the button before
you're even
there it does not matter K them W so to
be fair it would have been pretty tox if
you did get that I locked at the shovel
hit away the key that keeps
find there's so much text all of a
sudden I think we're supposed to guess
where they hit her or something let's
see
[Music]
we need a
shovel I guess you're supposed to get
the shovel and you're supposed to give
it to the Great Fairy and
then I don't think you necessarily need
to give it to the great Fair let's be
real here you're gonna need to give it
to her what did what did the uh what did
the upgrade even do it it's like a metal
detector oh right that's
right well we still have a path really
far down South we need to go to this is
where we come from yes we
[Music]
started yes let South this
been
there really we didn't go this
way
[Music]
I well I mean down cell
beuse the bomb to get rid of him
well like I said they're still down
South we got to
go oh you blew up those bomb
flowers
oh I guess it's a a I think it's for
green so
[Music]
you have to switch back the purple and
you can pick them up but
how
what a solo adventure for
Green
[Music]
Oh I had
to I don't think it stops me from
exiting at least
I think this is where we go when we get
the the shovel you're not a deu scrub so
why are you even here do you want to
help us really is that so that's a big
help I was in deep trouble cuz there
weren't enough deu scrubs now uh where
were you now were you the one who's
going to help too huh that I'll do fine
that'll do
fine the two of you are going to work
your tails off okay we're busy so go on
get started I'm making you the leader so
go and lead I hear that now I'm the
leader player one
leader all right time to get busy work
work work you ready I'm going to name
three items and I want you to remember
each of them I ain't repeating myself
then you go into the woods NAB them
bring them back and in order you hear
bomb grass water jar tell your pals to
get the items in that
order so we really just need uh
water you make any mistakes and you're
fired I get
moving who's
Dey I guess blue is is it that guy at
the very bottom there this Ste don't
Dole bring it here yeah that's
see where the heck do we get a water
[Music]
drawer okay where are we getting a water
dra did you see them
[Music]
you can't pick these
up gu I didn't make
[Music]
greed Powers
unite let's
go but number go
up what blue how how how D now even I
feel a little bad oh damage is done my
work
oh I found
[Music]
him
let's you think he wants his Rock no he
definitely does
[Music]
not now give Dey the good
news I need you to do
this oh you give to give that's not
right hang on I'm struggling over
here all right we'll give him the good
news
a nice work you're not as worthless as I
look you know what that that's it job's
done you did so well I'm going to give
you a special reward a power bracelet
put this on you can uh even lift the
heaviest
things yeah we could do that unlock some
area or
too little bit more for a shovel but
that's
get him out of
here tingle's coming tingle's coming
that's yours what are you talking about
that was yours how was that mine you
threw the you no I threw it on you and
you and it popped out of you that's
yours no that was from the that was from
the that was from all right fine
[Music]
okay why did I fall down
here yeah to much trouble Pi these
up let's go
[Music]
oh oh
shoot I'll pick up the trees and throw
them on
[Music]
the I can't they don't pick
up we can
leave yeah
I'm going to
die don't burn your health what are you
doing there's no Health in
here oh there
some oh I found the
Bell one of the middle
ones
prob what
the what what the heck was that I've
never seen that movie before but it's
been in all the games I've did it
earlier how do you do that you just keep
holding it
down oh
[Music]
cool oh so the bombs are down here too
okay I suppose I'll do the bombs well
hold up hold up uh we
need well you can actually change but I
need the Pegasus boots for one area
let's go to that area first then we can
come
back oh that that STL actually stopped
from taking
damage so there's tree to our left up
here not this one I mean sure we can do
this one but this
[Music]
isn't think there was one was it to the
one to the left here
[Music]
are we already on the other side no
we're
not going
that I think if we go up or down from
here let's try up
first oh heck yeah that
you're leaking bombs
there all right left left
this I don't remember the exact area is
basically two trees block the one
one all
right no not here
either I'm pretty sure it was down
was
it yeah at this point we checked all
above no left and left left and
down can't
[Music]
left left
again let's go
down I know was far to the left just
wonder know which uh
huh keep
going well sure we didn't go up no no I
don't think this is it this is the big
area oh well dang I'm
wrong oh and it turns out we can't do it
anyways while I can get across that Gap
I uh can't LIF the thing up with okay
whatever let's go back where we
were that's cool
[Music]
oh
right aren one of
[Applause]
okay here
is you pick bombs
[Music]
yeah it's like yeah sure as soon as I oh
my god do you see
it the moment I changed the direction
[Music]
dang look it's a bullet
h a bullet hell for
noobs ladies
thany oh we can't pick this
up I guess we could do like good the
thing is neither of us can get a cross
it
now it's like I guess it unlocks it in
the future if we get other items but
it's not really much of a reason to
there's nothing up right no it was this
boss boss Zone you've entered the boss
Zone this is where we put our
bosses all right get
[Music]
these I didn't do
it oh I didn't take any damage from that
[Music]
I can't get past it I got to burn
it at least they make you wear the
shield in the back so you know there's
[Music]
that oh they're all gone
oh now you're over laughing the
[Music]
music it says it shoots three arrows I'm
not I'm not seeing that you
know it's a lot oh man
[Music]
what does this guy have to
say
h
[Music]
oops I'll talk to
him uh I adore Lord gam but that shady
guy who looks like you ain't so great
he's not one of us but still pushes us
around like he's some kind of Big Shot
[Music]
I didn't even grab
that you still don't have a guy who can
actually like you know fight
with you got to make blue pick up your
um your thing for
you you know how to do that yeah you
yeah you do that and then you make get
thr down then make
blue there
a big brain now we got to go to the de
is in that up oh he just throws it try
roll no rolling for
you oh this
is still unlocks it even
with I guess I'll someone
bombs might be some bomb
all right so now the question is do you
know we got to upgrade it oh
right yeah
see that makes sense
[Music]
but don't you generally still have to be
pretty close to get the upgrade yep now
what are we looking for again areen we
looking for something yeah they hid the
key but we we found a key I know and
they hid
one do I have to dig to get the Chim no
it's just when you walk around and near
something go
first why are there bombs here what are
you doing
up here I didn't check this
[Music]
Hilaria we're good got a you know make
sure we cover our
track I heard I got an email let's check
our
tracks yeah that's not at all
I all right
what you got
there an
explosive you want to here next or what
we doing I have no clue where we're
[Music]
going watch it be like back at the
beginning like back on the first area
yeah
I guess while we're here we can check up
B
[Music]
coming no
beeping you don't hear
it my sound effects are a little low so
let me know if you do hear
it I don't know if it will play for me
since we
on I could hear it when you were doing
it oh really yeah I haven't heard
anything now
I mean
[Music]
nope I would imagine if you don't hear
the
[Music]
beeping dang it's kind of strangely
precise isn't
it oh no I messed it up dang that
sucks oh
so
close are you are you happy with
yourself
yeah why wouldn't I my beautiful
one left my mark on this lost
force all right let's probably off to
the right then my guess is it's probably
going to be at the beginning
but can you pick that up nope no I
[Music]
can't this
pushing oh right that was the shadow
I didn't do it can we dig in
there I guess have at
it no you cannot diing
there I don't hear any chime either well
what was that no it was just the smoke
effect
[Music]
D this is like the longest level of
allall start this before it was even
10:00 did pick up one of
them doesn't really matter well actually
maybe it does cuz I
can I'm not hear enough
and you're sure that it
wasn't only when you dog I'm pretty sure
it was when you
dog it was when you were walking around
it
got why ghost
they really should have used that
mechanic a little
more actual
puzles they use it for the one yeah so
far why are you wear bombs
everywhere like limiting where I can go
and
D come on
[Music]
was there any suspicious areas you think
could be
nope Link's having some problems there
is always dark
yeah not
here fine take them I didn't want him
[Music]
anyways St
fine I didn't want me
anyways green gy is going to
disappear well let me out I I already
hit the teleporter twice nowen disaar
that didn't make a bit of sense I hit
the darn teleporter and it Stills like
not I it's in here I hate how it like
undo your
formation oh I hear
something
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah wait how do I have a d now
that's
interesting oh
cussy oh boy oh he's got a bigger bomb
than
me right
right oh there give you
a n you can keep doing
[Music]
it I knew want the other
guy D look at this
garbage how
[Applause]
I don't want this dude take him
back well that's
it where's our boss
[Music]
you're
quiet what you
say um some snarky thing about um
politics and uh and the phones being
tracking devices
not not going to praise you for your
greed that's for
sure greed that's what that call
[Music]
represents unless it was my call then
it's
not then then it's Justice
did you hear about the new Intel
GPU yeah the ark The Arc
gpus the
b850 sounds like a
plane sounds like a bomber just
about apparently it's pretty
decent I mean it's like two generations
behind but it's also only 250 bucks
compared to nvidia's
like charge thousands for yeah if you're
going to do a starter build that
actually might be the very the most
ideal situation to be in yeah that's
what it's looking like although their
driver issues are going to have to get
worked out the next uh year or two
that's going to be a headache is the
driver information and all the things in
that
domain shoot I didn't mean to do
that I think that is a reasonably good
place to stop for today
I'm good with
[Music]
that well as they say comment subscribe
like hit it again Bell notification the
whole the whole nine
yards uh why aren't you doing the N
yards you should be doing all n yards
all of them the whole nine yards all of
it but on the n